{
    "exam_metadata": {
        "layout": "exam",
        "title": "Practice Exam 17",
        "exam_id": 17,
        "courseName": "AWS Cloud Practitioner",
        "difficulty": 1,
        "tags": [
            "aws",
            "cloud"
        ],
        "description": "Introduction exam"
    },
    "questions": [
        {
            "question_number": 2,
            "question_text": "When comparing AWS with on-premises Total Cost of Ownership (TCO), what costs are included?",
            "is_multiple_choice": false,
            "correct_answer_keys": "A",
            "correct_answer_text": "Data center security",
            "options": [
                {
                    "option_key": "A",
                    "option_text": "Data center security"
                },
                {
                    "option_key": "B",
                    "option_text": "Business analysis"
                },
                {
                    "option_key": "C",
                    "option_text": "Project management"
                },
                {
                    "option_key": "D",
                    "option_text": "Operating system administration"
                }
            ]
        },
        {
            "question_number": 3,
            "question_text": "According to the AWS shared responsibility model, what is AWS responsible for?",
            "is_multiple_choice": false,
            "correct_answer_keys": "D",
            "correct_answer_text": "Managing the network infrastructure",
            "options": [
                {
                    "option_key": "A",
                    "option_text": "Configuring Amazon VPC"
                },
                {
                    "option_key": "B",
                    "option_text": "Managing application code"
                },
                {
                    "option_key": "C",
                    "option_text": "Maintaining application traffic"
                },
                {
                    "option_key": "D",
                    "option_text": "Managing the network infrastructure"
                }
            ]
        },
        {
            "question_number": 4,
            "question_text": "Which service should be used to estimate the costs of running a new project on AWS?",
            "is_multiple_choice": false,
            "correct_answer_keys": "C",
            "correct_answer_text": "AWS Cost Explorer API",
            "options": [
                {
                    "option_key": "A",
                    "option_text": "AWS TCO Calculator"
                },
                {
                    "option_key": "B",
                    "option_text": "AWS Simple Monthly Calculator"
                },
                {
                    "option_key": "C",
                    "option_text": "AWS Cost Explorer API"
                },
                {
                    "option_key": "D",
                    "option_text": "AWS Budgets"
                }
            ]
        },
        {
            "question_number": 5,
            "question_text": "Which AWS tool will identify security groups that grant unrestricted Internet access to a limited list of ports?",
            "is_multiple_choice": false,
            "correct_answer_keys": "B",
            "correct_answer_text": "AWS Trusted Advisor",
            "options": [
                {
                    "option_key": "A",
                    "option_text": "AWS Organizations"
                },
                {
                    "option_key": "B",
                    "option_text": "AWS Trusted Advisor"
                },
                {
                    "option_key": "C",
                    "option_text": "AWS Usage Report"
                },
                {
                    "option_key": "D",
                    "option_text": "Amazon EC2 dashboard"
                }
            ]
        },
        {
            "question_number": 6,
            "question_text": "Which AWS service can be used to generate alerts based on an estimated monthly bill?",
            "is_multiple_choice": false,
            "correct_answer_keys": "B",
            "correct_answer_text": "Amazon CloudWatch",
            "options": [
                {
                    "option_key": "A",
                    "option_text": "AWS Config"
                },
                {
                    "option_key": "B",
                    "option_text": "Amazon CloudWatch"
                },
                {
                    "option_key": "C",
                    "option_text": "AWS X-Ray"
                },
                {
                    "option_key": "D",
                    "option_text": "AWS CloudTrail"
                }
            ]
        },
        {
            "question_number": 7,
            "question_text": "Which Amazon EC2 pricing model offers the MOST significant discount when compared to On-Demand Instances?",
            "is_multiple_choice": false,
            "correct_answer_keys": "C",
            "correct_answer_text": "All Upfront Reserved Instances for a 3-year term",
            "options": [
                {
                    "option_key": "A",
                    "option_text": "Partial Upfront Reserved Instances for a 1-year term"
                },
                {
                    "option_key": "B",
                    "option_text": "All Upfront Reserved Instances for a 1-year term"
                },
                {
                    "option_key": "C",
                    "option_text": "All Upfront Reserved Instances for a 3-year term"
                },
                {
                    "option_key": "D",
                    "option_text": "No Upfront Reserved Instances for a 3-year term"
                }
            ]
        },
        {
            "question_number": 8,
            "question_text": "Which of the following is the responsibility of AWS?",
            "is_multiple_choice": false,
            "correct_answer_keys": "B",
            "correct_answer_text": "Physically destroying storage media at end of life",
            "options": [
                {
                    "option_key": "A",
                    "option_text": "Setting up AWS Identity and Access Management (IAM) users and groups"
                },
                {
                    "option_key": "B",
                    "option_text": "Physically destroying storage media at end of life"
                },
                {
                    "option_key": "C",
                    "option_text": "Patching guest operating systems"
                },
                {
                    "option_key": "D",
                    "option_text": "Configuring security settings on Amazon EC2 instances"
                }
            ]
        },
        {
            "question_number": 9,
            "question_text": "Which of the following is an advantage of using AWS?",
            "is_multiple_choice": false,
            "correct_answer_keys": "C",
            "correct_answer_text": "There is no guessing on capacity needs.",
            "options": [
                {
                    "option_key": "A",
                    "option_text": "AWS audits user data."
                },
                {
                    "option_key": "B",
                    "option_text": "Data is automatically secure."
                },
                {
                    "option_key": "C",
                    "option_text": "There is no guessing on capacity needs."
                },
                {
                    "option_key": "D",
                    "option_text": "AWS manages compliance needs."
                }
            ]
        },
        {
            "question_number": 10,
            "question_text": "Which AWS service would a customer use with a static website to achieve lower latency and high transfer speeds?",
            "is_multiple_choice": false,
            "correct_answer_keys": "D",
            "correct_answer_text": "Amazon CloudFront",
            "options": [
                {
                    "option_key": "A",
                    "option_text": "AWS Lambda"
                },
                {
                    "option_key": "B",
                    "option_text": "Amazon DynamoDB Accelerator"
                },
                {
                    "option_key": "C",
                    "option_text": "Amazon Route 53"
                },
                {
                    "option_key": "D",
                    "option_text": "Amazon CloudFront"
                }
            ]
        },
        {
            "question_number": 11,
            "question_text": "Which services manage and automate application deployments on AWS? (Choose two.)",
            "is_multiple_choice": true,
            "correct_answer_keys": "A, D",
            "correct_answer_text": "AWS Elastic Beanstalk | AWS CloudFormation",
            "options": [
                {
                    "option_key": "A",
                    "option_text": "AWS Elastic Beanstalk"
                },
                {
                    "option_key": "B",
                    "option_text": "AWS CodeCommit"
                },
                {
                    "option_key": "C",
                    "option_text": "AWS Data Pipeline"
                },
                {
                    "option_key": "D",
                    "option_text": "AWS CloudFormation"
                },
                {
                    "option_key": "E",
                    "option_text": "AWS Config"
                }
            ]
        },
        {
            "question_number": 12,
            "question_text": "A user wants guidance on possible savings when migrating from on-premises to AWS. <br/> Which tool is suitable for this scenario?",
            "is_multiple_choice": false,
            "correct_answer_keys": "C",
            "correct_answer_text": "AWS Total Cost of Ownership (TCO) Calculator",
            "options": [
                {
                    "option_key": "A",
                    "option_text": "AWS Budgets"
                },
                {
                    "option_key": "B",
                    "option_text": "Cost Explorer"
                },
                {
                    "option_key": "C",
                    "option_text": "AWS Total Cost of Ownership (TCO) Calculator"
                },
                {
                    "option_key": "D",
                    "option_text": "AWS Well-Architected Tool"
                }
            ]
        },
        {
            "question_number": 13,
            "question_text": "Which principles are used to architect applications for reliability on the AWS Cloud? (Choose two.)",
            "is_multiple_choice": true,
            "correct_answer_keys": "A, B",
            "correct_answer_text": "Design for automated failure recovery | Use multiple Availability Zones",
            "options": [
                {
                    "option_key": "A",
                    "option_text": "Design for automated failure recovery"
                },
                {
                    "option_key": "B",
                    "option_text": "Use multiple Availability Zones"
                },
                {
                    "option_key": "C",
                    "option_text": "Manage changes via documented processes"
                },
                {
                    "option_key": "D",
                    "option_text": "Test for moderate demand to ensure reliability"
                },
                {
                    "option_key": "E",
                    "option_text": "Backup recovery to an on-premises environment"
                }
            ]
        },
        {
            "question_number": 14,
            "question_text": "What tasks should a customer perform when that customer suspects an AWS account has been compromised? (Choose two.)",
            "is_multiple_choice": true,
            "correct_answer_keys": "A, E",
            "correct_answer_text": "Rotate passwords and access keys. | Contact AWS Support.",
            "options": [
                {
                    "option_key": "A",
                    "option_text": "Rotate passwords and access keys."
                },
                {
                    "option_key": "B",
                    "option_text": "Remove MFA tokens."
                },
                {
                    "option_key": "C",
                    "option_text": "Move resources to a different AWS Region."
                },
                {
                    "option_key": "D",
                    "option_text": "Delete AWS CloudTrail Resources."
                },
                {
                    "option_key": "E",
                    "option_text": "Contact AWS Support."
                }
            ]
        },
        {
            "question_number": 15,
            "question_text": "What is an example of high availability in the AWS Cloud?",
            "is_multiple_choice": false,
            "correct_answer_keys": "B",
            "correct_answer_text": "Ensuring an application remains accessible, even if a resource fails",
            "options": [
                {
                    "option_key": "A",
                    "option_text": "Consulting AWS technical support at any time day or night"
                },
                {
                    "option_key": "B",
                    "option_text": "Ensuring an application remains accessible, even if a resource fails"
                },
                {
                    "option_key": "C",
                    "option_text": "Making any AWS service available for use by paying on demand"
                },
                {
                    "option_key": "D",
                    "option_text": "Deploying in any part of the world using AWS Regions"
                }
            ]
        },
        {
            "question_number": 16,
            "question_text": "Which AWS security service protects applications from distributed denial of service attacks with always-on detection and automatic inline mitigations?",
            "is_multiple_choice": false,
            "correct_answer_keys": "D",
            "correct_answer_text": "AWS Shield",
            "options": [
                {
                    "option_key": "A",
                    "option_text": "Amazon Inspector"
                },
                {
                    "option_key": "B",
                    "option_text": "AWS Web Application Firewall (AWS WAF)"
                },
                {
                    "option_key": "C",
                    "option_text": "Elastic Load Balancing (ELB)"
                },
                {
                    "option_key": "D",
                    "option_text": "AWS Shield"
                }
            ]
        },
        {
            "question_number": 17,
            "question_text": "A company wants to monitor the CPU usage of its Amazon EC2 resources. <br/> Which AWS service should the company use?",
            "is_multiple_choice": false,
            "correct_answer_keys": "B",
            "correct_answer_text": "Amazon CloudWatch",
            "options": [
                {
                    "option_key": "A",
                    "option_text": "AWS CloudTrail"
                },
                {
                    "option_key": "B",
                    "option_text": "Amazon CloudWatch"
                },
                {
                    "option_key": "C",
                    "option_text": "AWS Cost and Usage report"
                },
                {
                    "option_key": "D",
                    "option_text": "Amazon Simple Notification Service (Amazon SNS)"
                }
            ]
        },
        {
            "question_number": 18,
            "question_text": "What is an AWS Identity and Access Management (IAM) role?",
            "is_multiple_choice": false,
            "correct_answer_keys": "C",
            "correct_answer_text": "An entity that defines a set of permissions for use with an AWS resource",
            "options": [
                {
                    "option_key": "A",
                    "option_text": "A user associated with an AWS resource"
                },
                {
                    "option_key": "B",
                    "option_text": "A group associated with an AWS resource"
                },
                {
                    "option_key": "C",
                    "option_text": "An entity that defines a set of permissions for use with an AWS resource"
                },
                {
                    "option_key": "D",
                    "option_text": "An authentication credential associated with a multi-factor authentication (MFA) token"
                }
            ]
        },
        {
            "question_number": 19,
            "question_text": "What are the advantages of Reserved Instances? (Choose two.)",
            "is_multiple_choice": true,
            "correct_answer_keys": "A, E",
            "correct_answer_text": "They provide a discount over on-demand pricing. | Customers can reserve capacity in an Availability Zone.",
            "options": [
                {
                    "option_key": "A",
                    "option_text": "They provide a discount over on-demand pricing."
                },
                {
                    "option_key": "B",
                    "option_text": "They provide access to additional instance types."
                },
                {
                    "option_key": "C",
                    "option_text": "They provide additional networking capability."
                },
                {
                    "option_key": "D",
                    "option_text": "Customers can upgrade instances as new types become available."
                },
                {
                    "option_key": "E",
                    "option_text": "Customers can reserve capacity in an Availability Zone."
                }
            ]
        },
        {
            "question_number": 20,
            "question_text": "How do Amazon EC2 Auto Scaling groups help achieve high availability for a web application?",
            "is_multiple_choice": false,
            "correct_answer_keys": "B",
            "correct_answer_text": "They automatically add or replace instances across multiple Availability Zones when the application needs it.",
            "options": [
                {
                    "option_key": "A",
                    "option_text": "They automatically add more instances across multiple AWS Regions based on global demand of the application."
                },
                {
                    "option_key": "B",
                    "option_text": "They automatically add or replace instances across multiple Availability Zones when the application needs it."
                },
                {
                    "option_key": "C",
                    "option_text": "They enable the application's static content to reside closer to end users."
                },
                {
                    "option_key": "D",
                    "option_text": "They are able to distribute incoming requests across a tier of web server instances."
                }
            ]
        },
        {
            "question_number": 21,
            "question_text": "How can one AWS account use Reserved Instances from another AWS account?",
            "is_multiple_choice": false,
            "correct_answer_keys": "B",
            "correct_answer_text": "By using AWS Organizations consolidated billing",
            "options": [
                {
                    "option_key": "A",
                    "option_text": "By using Amazon EC2 Dedicated Instances"
                },
                {
                    "option_key": "B",
                    "option_text": "By using AWS Organizations consolidated billing"
                },
                {
                    "option_key": "C",
                    "option_text": "By using the AWS Cost Explorer tool"
                },
                {
                    "option_key": "D",
                    "option_text": "By using AWS Budgets"
                }
            ]
        },
        {
            "question_number": 22,
            "question_text": "A customer runs an On-Demand Amazon Linux EC2 instance for 3 hours, 5 minutes, and 6 seconds. <br/> For how much time will the customer be billed?",
            "is_multiple_choice": false,
            "correct_answer_keys": "B",
            "correct_answer_text": "3 hours, 5 minutes, and 6 seconds",
            "options": [
                {
                    "option_key": "A",
                    "option_text": "3 hours, 5 minutes"
                },
                {
                    "option_key": "B",
                    "option_text": "3 hours, 5 minutes, and 6 seconds"
                },
                {
                    "option_key": "C",
                    "option_text": "3 hours, 6 minutes"
                },
                {
                    "option_key": "D",
                    "option_text": "4 hours"
                }
            ]
        },
        {
            "question_number": 23,
            "question_text": "Which of the following AWS services provide compute resources? (Choose two.)",
            "is_multiple_choice": true,
            "correct_answer_keys": "A, B",
            "correct_answer_text": "AWS Lambda | Amazon Elastic Container Service (Amazon ECS)",
            "options": [
                {
                    "option_key": "A",
                    "option_text": "AWS Lambda"
                },
                {
                    "option_key": "B",
                    "option_text": "Amazon Elastic Container Service (Amazon ECS)"
                },
                {
                    "option_key": "C",
                    "option_text": "AWS CodeDeploy"
                },
                {
                    "option_key": "D",
                    "option_text": "Amazon Glacier"
                },
                {
                    "option_key": "E",
                    "option_text": "AWS Organizations"
                }
            ]
        },
        {
            "question_number": 24,
            "question_text": "Which AWS service enables users to deploy infrastructure as code by automating the process of provisioning resources?",
            "is_multiple_choice": false,
            "correct_answer_keys": "B",
            "correct_answer_text": "AWS CloudFormation",
            "options": [
                {
                    "option_key": "A",
                    "option_text": "Amazon GameLift"
                },
                {
                    "option_key": "B",
                    "option_text": "AWS CloudFormation"
                },
                {
                    "option_key": "C",
                    "option_text": "AWS Data Pipeline"
                },
                {
                    "option_key": "D",
                    "option_text": "AWS Glue"
                }
            ]
        },
        {
            "question_number": 25,
            "question_text": "Which AWS services provide a way to extend an on-premises architecture to the AWS Cloud? (Choose two.)",
            "is_multiple_choice": true,
            "correct_answer_keys": "B, D",
            "correct_answer_text": "AWS Direct Connect | AWS Storage Gateway",
            "options": [
                {
                    "option_key": "A",
                    "option_text": "Amazon EBS"
                },
                {
                    "option_key": "B",
                    "option_text": "AWS Direct Connect"
                },
                {
                    "option_key": "C",
                    "option_text": "Amazon CloudFront"
                },
                {
                    "option_key": "D",
                    "option_text": "AWS Storage Gateway"
                },
                {
                    "option_key": "E",
                    "option_text": "Amazon Connect"
                }
            ]
        },
        {
            "question_number": 26,
            "question_text": "Which of the following allows users to provision a dedicated network connection from their internal network to AWS?",
            "is_multiple_choice": false,
            "correct_answer_keys": "B",
            "correct_answer_text": "AWS Direct Connect",
            "options": [
                {
                    "option_key": "A",
                    "option_text": "AWS CloudHSM"
                },
                {
                    "option_key": "B",
                    "option_text": "AWS Direct Connect"
                },
                {
                    "option_key": "C",
                    "option_text": "AWS VPN"
                },
                {
                    "option_key": "D",
                    "option_text": "Amazon Connect"
                }
            ]
        },
        {
            "question_number": 27,
            "question_text": "Which services use AWS edge locations? (Choose two.)",
            "is_multiple_choice": true,
            "correct_answer_keys": "A, B",
            "correct_answer_text": "Amazon CloudFront | AWS Shield",
            "options": [
                {
                    "option_key": "A",
                    "option_text": "Amazon CloudFront"
                },
                {
                    "option_key": "B",
                    "option_text": "AWS Shield"
                },
                {
                    "option_key": "C",
                    "option_text": "Amazon EC2"
                },
                {
                    "option_key": "D",
                    "option_text": "Amazon RDS"
                },
                {
                    "option_key": "E",
                    "option_text": "Amazon ElastiCache"
                }
            ]
        },
        {
            "question_number": 28,
            "question_text": "Which service would provide network connectivity in a hybrid architecture that includes the AWS Cloud?",
            "is_multiple_choice": false,
            "correct_answer_keys": "A",
            "correct_answer_text": "Amazon VPC",
            "options": [
                {
                    "option_key": "A",
                    "option_text": "Amazon VPC"
                },
                {
                    "option_key": "B",
                    "option_text": "AWS Direct Connect"
                },
                {
                    "option_key": "C",
                    "option_text": "AWS Directory Service"
                },
                {
                    "option_key": "D",
                    "option_text": "Amazon API Gateway"
                }
            ]
        },
        {
            "question_number": 29,
            "question_text": "Which tool can be used to compare the costs of running a web application in a traditional hosting environment to running it on AWS?",
            "is_multiple_choice": false,
            "correct_answer_keys": "D",
            "correct_answer_text": "AWS Total Cost of Ownership (TCO) Calculator",
            "options": [
                {
                    "option_key": "A",
                    "option_text": "AWS Cost Explorer"
                },
                {
                    "option_key": "B",
                    "option_text": "AWS Budgets"
                },
                {
                    "option_key": "C",
                    "option_text": "AWS Cost and Usage report"
                },
                {
                    "option_key": "D",
                    "option_text": "AWS Total Cost of Ownership (TCO) Calculator"
                }
            ]
        },
        {
            "question_number": 30,
            "question_text": "What is the value of using third-party software from AWS Marketplace instead of installing third-party software on Amazon EC2? (Choose two.)",
            "is_multiple_choice": true,
            "correct_answer_keys": "A, B",
            "correct_answer_text": "Users pay for software by the hour or month depending on licensing. | AWS Marketplace enables the user to launch applications with 1-Click.",
            "options": [
                {
                    "option_key": "A",
                    "option_text": "Users pay for software by the hour or month depending on licensing."
                },
                {
                    "option_key": "B",
                    "option_text": "AWS Marketplace enables the user to launch applications with 1-Click."
                },
                {
                    "option_key": "C",
                    "option_text": "AWS Marketplace data encryption is managed by a third-party vendor."
                },
                {
                    "option_key": "D",
                    "option_text": "AWS Marketplace eliminates the need to upgrade to newer software versions."
                },
                {
                    "option_key": "E",
                    "option_text": "Users can deploy third-party software without testing."
                }
            ]
        },
        {
            "question_number": 31,
            "question_text": "Which of the following is a cloud architectural design principle?",
            "is_multiple_choice": false,
            "correct_answer_keys": "B",
            "correct_answer_text": "Loosely couple components.",
            "options": [
                {
                    "option_key": "A",
                    "option_text": "Scale up, not out."
                },
                {
                    "option_key": "B",
                    "option_text": "Loosely couple components."
                },
                {
                    "option_key": "C",
                    "option_text": "Build monolithic systems."
                },
                {
                    "option_key": "D",
                    "option_text": "Use commercial database software."
                }
            ]
        },
        {
            "question_number": 32,
            "question_text": "Under the shared responsibility model; which of the following areas are the customer's responsibility? (Choose two.)",
            "is_multiple_choice": true,
            "correct_answer_keys": "B, E",
            "correct_answer_text": "Patching of operating systems | Configuration of the security group",
            "options": [
                {
                    "option_key": "A",
                    "option_text": "Firmware upgrades of network infrastructure"
                },
                {
                    "option_key": "B",
                    "option_text": "Patching of operating systems"
                },
                {
                    "option_key": "C",
                    "option_text": "Patching of the underlying hypervisor"
                },
                {
                    "option_key": "D",
                    "option_text": "Physical security of data centers"
                },
                {
                    "option_key": "E",
                    "option_text": "Configuration of the security group"
                }
            ]
        },
        {
            "question_number": 33,
            "question_text": "Which service enables customers to audit and monitor changes in AWS resources?",
            "is_multiple_choice": false,
            "correct_answer_keys": "D",
            "correct_answer_text": "AWS Config",
            "options": [
                {
                    "option_key": "A",
                    "option_text": "AWS Trusted Advisor"
                },
                {
                    "option_key": "B",
                    "option_text": "Amazon GuardDuty"
                },
                {
                    "option_key": "C",
                    "option_text": "Amazon Inspector"
                },
                {
                    "option_key": "D",
                    "option_text": "AWS Config"
                }
            ]
        },
        {
            "question_number": 34,
            "question_text": "Which AWS service identifies security groups that allow unrestricted access to a user's AWS resources?",
            "is_multiple_choice": false,
            "correct_answer_keys": "B",
            "correct_answer_text": "AWS Trusted Advisor",
            "options": [
                {
                    "option_key": "A",
                    "option_text": "AWS CloudTrail"
                },
                {
                    "option_key": "B",
                    "option_text": "AWS Trusted Advisor"
                },
                {
                    "option_key": "C",
                    "option_text": "Amazon CloudWatch"
                },
                {
                    "option_key": "D",
                    "option_text": "Amazon Inspector"
                }
            ]
        },
        {
            "question_number": 35,
            "question_text": "According to the AWS shared responsibility model, who is responsible for configuration management?",
            "is_multiple_choice": false,
            "correct_answer_keys": "C",
            "correct_answer_text": "It is shared between AWS and the customer.",
            "options": [
                {
                    "option_key": "A",
                    "option_text": "It is solely the responsibility of the customer."
                },
                {
                    "option_key": "B",
                    "option_text": "It is solely the responsibility of AWS."
                },
                {
                    "option_key": "C",
                    "option_text": "It is shared between AWS and the customer."
                },
                {
                    "option_key": "D",
                    "option_text": "It is not part of the AWS shared responsibility model."
                }
            ]
        },
        {
            "question_number": 36,
            "question_text": "Which AWS service is a content delivery network that securely delivers data, video, and applications to users globally with low latency and high speeds?",
            "is_multiple_choice": false,
            "correct_answer_keys": "C",
            "correct_answer_text": "Amazon CloudFront",
            "options": [
                {
                    "option_key": "A",
                    "option_text": "AWS CloudFormation"
                },
                {
                    "option_key": "B",
                    "option_text": "AWS Direct Connect"
                },
                {
                    "option_key": "C",
                    "option_text": "Amazon CloudFront"
                },
                {
                    "option_key": "D",
                    "option_text": "Amazon Pinpoint"
                }
            ]
        },
        {
            "question_number": 37,
            "question_text": "Which benefit of the AWS Cloud supports matching the supply of resources with changing workload demands?",
            "is_multiple_choice": false,
            "correct_answer_keys": "C",
            "correct_answer_text": "Elasticity",
            "options": [
                {
                    "option_key": "A",
                    "option_text": "Security"
                },
                {
                    "option_key": "B",
                    "option_text": "Reliability"
                },
                {
                    "option_key": "C",
                    "option_text": "Elasticity"
                },
                {
                    "option_key": "D",
                    "option_text": "High availability"
                }
            ]
        },
        {
            "question_number": 38,
            "question_text": "A user is running an application on AWS and notices that one or more AWS-owned IP addresses is involved in a distributed denial-of-service (DDoS) attack. <br/> Who should the user contact FIRST about this situation?",
            "is_multiple_choice": false,
            "correct_answer_keys": "D",
            "correct_answer_text": "AWS Abuse team",
            "options": [
                {
                    "option_key": "A",
                    "option_text": "AWS Premium Support"
                },
                {
                    "option_key": "B",
                    "option_text": "AWS Technical Account Manager"
                },
                {
                    "option_key": "C",
                    "option_text": "AWS Solutions Architect"
                },
                {
                    "option_key": "D",
                    "option_text": "AWS Abuse team"
                }
            ]
        },
        {
            "question_number": 39,
            "question_text": "Which of the following are benefits of hosting infrastructure in the AWS Cloud? (Choose two.)",
            "is_multiple_choice": true,
            "correct_answer_keys": "A, C",
            "correct_answer_text": "There are no upfront commitments. | Users have the ability to provision resources on demand.",
            "options": [
                {
                    "option_key": "A",
                    "option_text": "There are no upfront commitments."
                },
                {
                    "option_key": "B",
                    "option_text": "AWS manages all security in the cloud."
                },
                {
                    "option_key": "C",
                    "option_text": "Users have the ability to provision resources on demand."
                },
                {
                    "option_key": "D",
                    "option_text": "Users have access to free and unlimited storage."
                },
                {
                    "option_key": "E",
                    "option_text": "Users have control over the physical infrastructure."
                }
            ]
        },
        {
            "question_number": 40,
            "question_text": "What AWS service would be used to centrally manage AWS access policies across multiple accounts?",
            "is_multiple_choice": false,
            "correct_answer_keys": "D",
            "correct_answer_text": "AWS Organizations",
            "options": [
                {
                    "option_key": "A",
                    "option_text": "AWS Service Catalog"
                },
                {
                    "option_key": "B",
                    "option_text": "AWS Config"
                },
                {
                    "option_key": "C",
                    "option_text": "AWS Trusted Advisor"
                },
                {
                    "option_key": "D",
                    "option_text": "AWS Organizations"
                }
            ]
        },
        {
            "question_number": 41,
            "question_text": "What is AWS Trusted Advisor?",
            "is_multiple_choice": false,
            "correct_answer_keys": "C",
            "correct_answer_text": "It is an online tool with a set of automated checks that provides recommendations on cost optimization, performance, and security.",
            "options": [
                {
                    "option_key": "A",
                    "option_text": "It is an AWS staff member who provides recommendations and best practices on how to use AWS."
                },
                {
                    "option_key": "B",
                    "option_text": "It is a network of AWS partners who provide recommendations and best practices on how to use AWS."
                },
                {
                    "option_key": "C",
                    "option_text": "It is an online tool with a set of automated checks that provides recommendations on cost optimization, performance, and security."
                },
                {
                    "option_key": "D",
                    "option_text": "It is another name for AWS Technical Account Managers who provide recommendations on cost optimization, performance, and security."
                }
            ]
        },
        {
            "question_number": 42,
            "question_text": "Which AWS service or feature allows a company to visualize, understand, and manage AWS costs and usage over time?",
            "is_multiple_choice": false,
            "correct_answer_keys": "B",
            "correct_answer_text": "AWS Cost Explorer",
            "options": [
                {
                    "option_key": "A",
                    "option_text": "AWS Budgets"
                },
                {
                    "option_key": "B",
                    "option_text": "AWS Cost Explorer"
                },
                {
                    "option_key": "C",
                    "option_text": "AWS Organizations"
                },
                {
                    "option_key": "D",
                    "option_text": "Consolidated billing"
                }
            ]
        },
        {
            "question_number": 43,
            "question_text": "Which AWS service offers on-demand access to AWS security and compliance reports?",
            "is_multiple_choice": false,
            "correct_answer_keys": "B",
            "correct_answer_text": "AWS Artifact",
            "options": [
                {
                    "option_key": "A",
                    "option_text": "AWS CloudTrail"
                },
                {
                    "option_key": "B",
                    "option_text": "AWS Artifact"
                },
                {
                    "option_key": "C",
                    "option_text": "AWS Health"
                },
                {
                    "option_key": "D",
                    "option_text": "Amazon CloudWatch"
                }
            ]
        },
        {
            "question_number": 44,
            "question_text": "What are the benefits of using the AWS Cloud for companies with customers in many countries around the world? (Choose two.)",
            "is_multiple_choice": true,
            "correct_answer_keys": "A, C",
            "correct_answer_text": "Companies can deploy applications in multiple AWS Regions to reduce latency. | Amazon CloudFront has multiple edge locations around the world to reduce latency.",
            "options": [
                {
                    "option_key": "A",
                    "option_text": "Companies can deploy applications in multiple AWS Regions to reduce latency."
                },
                {
                    "option_key": "B",
                    "option_text": "Amazon Translate automatically translates third-party website interfaces into multiple languages."
                },
                {
                    "option_key": "C",
                    "option_text": "Amazon CloudFront has multiple edge locations around the world to reduce latency."
                },
                {
                    "option_key": "D",
                    "option_text": "Amazon Comprehend allows users to build applications that can respond to user requests in many languages."
                },
                {
                    "option_key": "E",
                    "option_text": "Elastic Load Balancing can distribute application web traffic to multiple AWS Regions around the world, which reduces latency."
                }
            ]
        },
        {
            "question_number": 45,
            "question_text": "Which AWS service handles the deployment details of capacity provisioning, load balancing, Auto Scaling, and application health monitoring?",
            "is_multiple_choice": false,
            "correct_answer_keys": "B",
            "correct_answer_text": "AWS Elastic Beanstalk",
            "options": [
                {
                    "option_key": "A",
                    "option_text": "AWS Config"
                },
                {
                    "option_key": "B",
                    "option_text": "AWS Elastic Beanstalk"
                },
                {
                    "option_key": "C",
                    "option_text": "Amazon Route 53"
                },
                {
                    "option_key": "D",
                    "option_text": "Amazon CloudFront"
                }
            ]
        },
        {
            "question_number": 46,
            "question_text": "Which AWS service provides inbound and outbound network ACLs to harden external connectivity to Amazon EC2?",
            "is_multiple_choice": false,
            "correct_answer_keys": "C",
            "correct_answer_text": "Amazon VPC",
            "options": [
                {
                    "option_key": "A",
                    "option_text": "AWS IAM"
                },
                {
                    "option_key": "B",
                    "option_text": "Amazon Connect"
                },
                {
                    "option_key": "C",
                    "option_text": "Amazon VPC"
                },
                {
                    "option_key": "D",
                    "option_text": "Amazon API Gateway"
                }
            ]
        },
        {
            "question_number": 47,
            "question_text": "When a company provisions web servers in multiple AWS Regions, what is being increased?",
            "is_multiple_choice": false,
            "correct_answer_keys": "B",
            "correct_answer_text": "Availability",
            "options": [
                {
                    "option_key": "A",
                    "option_text": "Coupling"
                },
                {
                    "option_key": "B",
                    "option_text": "Availability"
                },
                {
                    "option_key": "C",
                    "option_text": "Security"
                },
                {
                    "option_key": "D",
                    "option_text": "Durability"
                }
            ]
        },
        {
            "question_number": 48,
            "question_text": "The pay-as-you-go pricing model for AWS services:",
            "is_multiple_choice": false,
            "correct_answer_keys": "A",
            "correct_answer_text": "reduces capital expenditures.",
            "options": [
                {
                    "option_key": "A",
                    "option_text": "reduces capital expenditures."
                },
                {
                    "option_key": "B",
                    "option_text": "requires payment up front for AWS services."
                },
                {
                    "option_key": "C",
                    "option_text": "is relevant only for Amazon EC2, Amazon S3, and Amazon RDS."
                },
                {
                    "option_key": "D",
                    "option_text": "reduces operational expenditures."
                }
            ]
        },
        {
            "question_number": 49,
            "question_text": "Under the AWS shared responsibility model, AWS is responsible for which security-related task?",
            "is_multiple_choice": false,
            "correct_answer_keys": "B",
            "correct_answer_text": "Physical security of global infrastructure",
            "options": [
                {
                    "option_key": "A",
                    "option_text": "Lifecycle management of IAM credentials"
                },
                {
                    "option_key": "B",
                    "option_text": "Physical security of global infrastructure"
                },
                {
                    "option_key": "C",
                    "option_text": "Encryption of Amazon EBS volumes"
                },
                {
                    "option_key": "D",
                    "option_text": "Firewall configuration"
                }
            ]
        },
        {
            "question_number": 50,
            "question_text": "Which AWS service enables users to consolidate billing across multiple accounts?",
            "is_multiple_choice": false,
            "correct_answer_keys": "B",
            "correct_answer_text": "AWS Organizations",
            "options": [
                {
                    "option_key": "A",
                    "option_text": "Amazon QuickSight"
                },
                {
                    "option_key": "B",
                    "option_text": "AWS Organizations"
                },
                {
                    "option_key": "C",
                    "option_text": "AWS Budgets"
                },
                {
                    "option_key": "D",
                    "option_text": "Amazon Forecast"
                }
            ]
        }
    ]
}